http://www.fev.com/legal-notice.html

We use cookies to improve your experience on our Website. We need cookies to continually improve our services, enable certain features, and when we embed third-party services or content, such as the Vimeo video player or Twitter feeds. In such cases, information may also be transferred to third parties. By using our website, you agree to the use of cookies. We use different types of cookies. You can personalize your cookie settings here:
Show detail settings
Necessary cookies
Only cookies permitted that are required for the basic functionality of our websites.
Statistical and marketing cookies
Permit cookies that help us to analyse the page views and user behavior on our websites. We only use this information for improving our services.
Please find more information in our privacy statement.
There you may also change your settings later.
Save options
I agree
Toggle navigation
Menu
What we doWho we areCareersComing up
What we doVehicle DevelopmentPowertrain Development & ElectrificationIntelligent Mobility & SoftwareSoftware and Testing SolutionsConsultingWho we areManagementLocationsValuesCompany HistoryQuality, Project Management, Occupational & Environmental SafetyCareersCurrent OpeningsUnsolicited ApplicationIntroducing FEVRecruitment EventsContactComing upFEV ConferencesExhibitionsOnline SeminarsWhitepapersCustomer NewslettersPressCorona InformationVehicle DevelopmentVehicle ArchitectureChassis and Electric & ElectronicsBody in WhiteExterior and InteriorLightingVehicle PerformanceProductionPowertrain Development & ElectrificationAerodynamics & Flow AnalysesAdvanced ApplicationsBenchmarkingCommercial and Industrial PowertrainsE-MobilityFuelsLarge Bore EnginesNVH – Noise Vibration HarshnessOff-HighwayPassenger Car & Light Commercial Diesel PowertrainsPassenger Car Gasoline PowertrainsProduction & Value EngineeringTransmission SystemsTurbochargingIntelligent Mobility & SoftwareAssisted & Automated DrivingConnected MobilitySystems EngineeringFunctional SafetyCybersecurityVehicles ElectronicsSoftwareData ScienceSoftware and Testing SolutionsTest CenterTest BenchesProductsAutomated Test SystemsService and MaintenanceDownload CenterEmbedded Systems DevelopmentContactConsultingManagementLocationsGermanyUSAChinaFranceIndiaAustriaBrazilItalyJapanMexicoNetherlandsPolandRomaniaRussiaSouth KoreaSpainSwedenTaiwanThailandTurkeyUnited KingdomVietnamValuesCompany HistoryQuality, Project Management, Occupational & Environmental SafetyCurrent OpeningsJobs in EuropeJobs in AsiaJobs in AmericaUnsolicited ApplicationIntroducing FEVRecruitment EventsContactFEV ConferencesFEV Conference - Zero CO2 MobilityFEV Conference - Diesel Powertrains 3.0Aachen Acoustics ColloquiumFEV Tech DaysExhibitionsOnline SeminarsWhitepapersShared MobilityEnergy StorageHigh Tech or Low CostCustomer NewslettersFEV SpectrumFEV Spectrum ArchivesFEV China NewsletterEngineering NewsletterPressPress ReleasesPress mailing listYour ContactCorona Information
Languages & Countries
LanguagesEnglishGermanChineseJapaneseCountriesGermanyUSABrazilUnited KingdomSwedenFranceItalySpainPolandRomaniaChinaIndiaJapanTurkeyTaiwan
Imprint and Data ProtectionRESPONSIBLE FOR DATA PROCESSING
Authorized representative of the Managing Board
Prof. Dr.-Ing. Stefan PischingerChairman of the Board and Managing Partner of FEV Group GmbH
Jürgen KoopsingravenCFO and Managing Director of FEV Group GmbH, globally responsible for Finance, Controlling, Human Resources, IT, Purchasing, Quality and Legal Affairs
Dr. Michael WilhelmExecutive Vice President of FEV Group GmbH and Chief Sales Officer (CSO), worldwide responsible for sales
Dr. Ulrich PfahlChairman of the Executive Board of FEV Asia GmbH, responsible for the Asian Business and Daughter Companies
Dr.-Ing. Patrick HupperichManaging Director of FEV North America Inc.
Dr.-Ing. Norbert W. AltChairman of the Management Board of FEV Europe GmbH, responsible for European business
Controller (person responsible) of content according to § 5 of the German Telemedia Act and § 55 of the Broadcasting Treaty
FEV Europe GmbHCorporate CommunicationsUlrich AndreeNeuenhofstraße 18152078 Aachen, Germany
Email presse@fev.com
Tel. +49 241 5689 8415Fax +49 241 5689 119
Registered office: AachenRegister court: Municipal court of AachenCommercial register no.: HRB 19139VAT identification number: DE297341822
Data Protection Officer contact:
Scheja und Partner Rechtsanwäte mbHKontakt: Herr Jens – Martin HeidemannAdenauerallee 136, 53113 Bonn
T: +49 228 227226-0F.: +49228 227226-26
Email: contact form - Incoming messages are treated confidentially.
If you have general questions about data protection, please send an email at contact@fev-news.com.
GENERAL INFORMATION ON DATA PROCESSING
Scope of personal data processing
We only collect and use personal data of our users as it is improves the functionality of our website, as well as our contents and services. The collection and use of personal data of our users takes place regularly and only with the user's consent. An exception applies in those cases where prior consent cannot be obtained for real reasons and the processing of the data is permitted by law.
Legal basis for the processing of personal data
Since we obtain the consent of the data subject for the processing of personal data, Art. 6 (1) (a) General Data Protection Regulation (GDPR) serves as the legal basis for the processing of personal data.
In the processing of personal data required for the performance of a contract to which the data subject is a party, Art. 6 (1) (b) GDPR serves as the legal basis. This also applies to processing operations that are necessary to carry out pre-contractual measures.
Because the processing of personal data is required to fulfill a legal obligation to which our company is subject, Art. 6 (1) (c) GDPR serves as the legal basis.
In the event that the vital interests of the data subject or another natural person require the processing of personal data, Art. 6 (1) (d) GDPR serves as the legal basis.
If processing is necessary to safeguard a legitimate interest of our company or a third party and if the interests, fundamental rights and freedoms of the data subject do not outweigh the first-mentioned interest, Art. 6 (1) (f) GDPR serves as the legal basis for processing.
Data deletion and storage time
The personal data of the data subject will be deleted or blocked as soon as the purpose of storage ceases to apply. Furthermore, data may be stored if this has been provided for by the European or national legislator in EU regulations, laws or other provisions to which the controller is subject. The data will also be blocked or deleted if a storage period prescribed by the aforementioned standards expires, unless there is a need for further storage of the data for the conclusion or fulfillment of a contract.
PROVISION OF THE WEBSITE AND CREATION OF LOG FILES
Description and scope of data processing
Every time you visit our website, our system automatically collects data and information from the user’s computer system.
The following data is collected:
(1) Information about the browser type and version used(2) The user's operating system(3) The user's Internet service provider(4) The IP address of the user(5) Date and time of access(6) Websites from which the user's system reaches our website (7) Websites accessed by the user's system through our website
The data is also stored in the log files of our system. The IP addresses of the user or other data that enables the assignment of the data to a user are not affected by this. This data is not stored together with other personal data of the user.
Legal basis for data processing
The legal basis for the temporary storage of data is Art. 6 (1) (f) GDPR.
Purpose of data processing
The temporary storage of the IP address by the system is necessary to enable the website to be delivered to the user's computer. For this, the IP address of the user must remain stored for the duration of the session.
These purposes also constitute our legitimate interest in data processing pursuant to Art. 6 (1) (f) GDPR.
Duration of retention
The data will be deleted as soon as it is no longer necessary to achieve the purpose for which it was collected. The collection of data for the provision of the website occurs until the respective session has ended.
Right to objection and removal
The collection of data for the provision of the website and the storage of data in log files is absolutely necessary for the operation of the website. Consequently, there is no possibility of objection on the part of the user.
USE OF COOKIESDescription and scope of data processing
We use cookies on our websites. Cookies are text files that are stored in the Internet browser or by the Internet browser on the user's computer system. If a user visits a website, a cookie may be stored on the user's operating system. This cookie contains a distinctive character string that enables a unique identification of the browser when the website is called up again.
We use cookies to make our website more user-friendly. Some elements of our website require the requesting browser to be identified even after a page change.
The following data is stored and transmitted in the cookies:
(1) Language settings(2) Log-in information
We also use cookies on our website which enable the analysis of the user's surfing behavior.
In this way, the following data can be transmitted:
(1) Search terms entered(2) Frequency of page views(3) Use of website functions
The user data collected in this way is pseudonymized using technical measures. Therefore it is no longer possible to assign the data to the calling user. The relevant data will not be stored together with other personal data of the users.
When accessing our website, users are informed by an information banner about the use of cookies for analysis purposes and referred to this privacy policy. It is possible to prevent the storage of cookies in the browser settings.
Legal basis for data processing
The legal basis for the processing of personal data using cookies is Art. 6 (1) (f) GDPR.
Purpose of data processing
The purpose of using technically necessary cookies is to simplify the use of websites for users. Some functions of our website cannot be offered without the use of cookies. For these, it is necessary that the browser is recognized even after a page change.
We need cookies for the following applications:
(1) Accepting language settings(2) Remembering search terms(3) Google Analytics
The user data collected by technically necessary cookies are not used to create user profiles.
The analysis cookies are used to improve the quality of our website and its content. The analysis cookies enable us to learn how the website is used and can thus continuously optimize our website.
These purposes also reflect our legitimate interest in the processing of personal data pursuant to Art. 6 (1) (f) GDPR.
Duration of storage and possibility of objection and elimination
Cookies are stored on the user’s computer and transmitted to us. Accordingly, you as a user also have full control over the use of cookies. By changing the settings in your Internet browser, you can disable or restrict the transmission of cookies. Cookies that have already been saved can be erased at any time. This can also be done automatically. If cookies are disabled for our website, it may no longer be possible to use all functions of the website in full.
Change your cookie-settings
We use cookies to improve your experience on our Website. We need cookies to continually improve our services, enable certain features, and when we embed third-party services or content, such as the Vimeo video player or Twitter feeds. In such cases, information may also be transferred to third parties. By using our website, you agree to the use of cookies. We use different types of cookies. You can personalize your cookie settings here:
Necessary cookies
Only cookies permitted that are required for the basic functionality of our websites.
Statistical and marketing cookies
Permit cookies that help us to analyse the page views and user behavior on our websites. We only use this information for improving our services.
I agree
GOOGLE SERVICES
This website uses Google Analytics, YouTube, Google Tag Manager,
Google Maps, and Google Fonts. If your main place of residence is inside
the European Economic Area or Switzerland, these services are provided
to you – unless specified in additional terms and conditions – by Google
Ireland Ltd. ("Google"), a company registered (register number 368047)
and operated under Irish law and headquartered at Gordon House, Barrow
Street, Dublin 4, Ireland.
You can find an excerpt of the current terms of use as well as Google’s privacy statement at:
https://policies.google.com/privacy
https://policies.google.com/termsBecause Google operates servers around the world, we cannot rule
out the possibility that personal information will be continue to be
shared with Google LLC, headquartered in the US. Google is certified
under the EU-U.S. Privacy Shield Framework. You can view the current
certification at www.privacyshield.gov/list. The EU-U.S. Privacy
Shield Framework is an informal agreement in the area of data
protection law negotiated between the European Union and the United
States of America between 2015 and 2016. It consists of a series of
commitments made by the US federal government and a resolution adopted
by the EU Commission. The Commission decided on July 12, 2016, that the
criteria of the Privacy Shield Framework correlate with the European
Union’s data protection requirements. The agreement has been applicable
since that time.
GOOGLE ANALYTICS
This website uses the web analysis tool "Google Analytics." The
purpose of this use is the "demand-oriented design" of this website,
which is carried out on the basis of a balance of interests. Web
analysis also enables us to identify and correct errors on the website,
e.g. through incorrect links. Google Analytics uses so-called "cookies."
These are text files that are stored on your computer that enable an
analysis of your use of the website. "Client IDs" are used to create
pseudonymous user profiles that jointly record the use of the websites
by desktop computers and mobile devices by a user.
The information generated by the cookie about your use of this
website is usually transferred to a Google server in the USA and stored
there. However, since we have activated IP anonymization on this website
and concluded a corresponding order-processing agreement with Google,
Google will shorten your IP address within member states of the European
Union or in other states party to the Agreement on the European
Economic Area beforehand. Only in exceptional cases will the full IP
address be transmitted to a Google server in the USA and shortened
there.
The anonymized IP address sent by your browser through your use of
Google Analytics will not be combined with other data owned by Google.
In these exceptions, your data will be processed in accordance with Art.
6, para. 1f of the GDPR on the basis of our legitimate interest in
statistical analysis of user behavior for purposes of optimization and
marketing. On our behalf, Google will use that information to evaluate
your use of our website in order to compile reports about website
activities and to provide us with other services in connection with
website and Internet usage.
You can prevent Google from collecting the data generated by the
cookie and data relating to your use of the website (including your IP
address) and from processing this data by Google by downloading and
installing the browser plug-in available under the following link: http://tools.google.com/dlpage/gaoptout?hl=en
GOOGLE WEB FONTS
We use so-called Google Web fonts on our Internet pages. The fonts
are loaded by servers from Google that provide a better design of the
website. The data processing is based on a balance of interests whereby
our interest lies in an appropriate design of the website.
The relevant fonts are loaded from the Google servers which are
generally located in the USA. The adequate data protection level is
guaranteed by Google within the context of a privacy shield.
SOCIAL MEDIA
We use social media channels as a supplementary service and provide
additional information there. Our website contains links to these social
media channels. We do not use so-called "social Plugins" (such as the
Facebook “Like” button). The links are only included in the web
analysis. We link to our website on the following social media channels:
LinkedIn: https://www.linkedin.com/company/67907
Facebook: https://www.facebook.com/pages/FEV-GmbH/171136272897772
Twitter: https://twitter.com/FEV_Europe_GmbH
Xing: http://www.xing.com/companies/fevgmbh
Youtube: https://www.youtube.com/user/FEVvideo
The social media platforms are independent information offerings and
independent of the FEV website. Further information on the purpose and
extent of data collection and the further processing and use of data by
the relevant social media service can be retrieved from the Internet
under the following URLs:
LinkedIn privacy policy: https://www.linkedin.com/legal/privacy-policy
Facebook privacy policy: https://www.facebook.com/privacy/
Twitter privacy policy: https://twitter.com/en/privacy
Xing privacy policy: https://privacy.xing.com/en/privacy-policy
YouTube privacy policy: https://policies.google.com/privacy?hl=en&gl=en
NewsletterDescription and scope of data processing
You can subscribe to a free e-mail newsletter on our website. When
registering for the newsletter, the data entered into the input mask is
transmitted to us.
In addition, the following data is collected upon registration:
(1) IP address of the calling computer(2) Date and time of registration
For processing of data in the newsletter mentioned below, the user’s
consent is obtained as part of the registration process and reference is
made to this Privacy Policy.
No data is passed on to any third parties in connection with data
processing for the purpose of sending newsletters. The data is used
exclusively for sending the newsletter.
Legal basis for data processing
The legal basis for the processing of data after registration for the newsletter by the user is Art. 6 (1) (a) GDPR.
Purpose of data processing
The purpose of collecting the user’s e-mail address is to send the user the newsletter.
The collection of other personal data as part of the registration
process serves to prevent misuse of the services or of the email address
used.
Duration of retention
The data will be deleted as soon as it is no longer necessary to
achieve the purpose for which it was collected. The user’s e-mail
address will be stored as long as the subscription to the information
service is active.
The other personal data collected during the registration process will generally be deleted after a period of seven days.
Right to objection and removal
The subscription to the newsletter can be canceled by the user at any
time. To this end, each newsletter contains a corresponding notice.
This also makes it possible to revoke the consent to storage of personal data collected during the registration process.
REGISTRATIONDescription and scope of data processing
On our website, we offer users the opportunity to register by
providing personal data. The data is entered into an input mask and
transmitted to us and saved. The data will not be passed on to third
parties. The following data is collected during the registration
process:
(1) E-mail address(2) Name(3) User name(4) Company name
At the time of registration, the following data is also stored:
(1) The IP address of the user(2) Date and time of registration
During the registration process, the user's consent to the processing of this data is obtained.
Legal basis for data processing
The legal basis for the processing of the data if the user has given their consent is Art. 6 (1) (a) GDPR.
Purpose of data processing
Registration of the user is necessary for the provision of certain contents and services on our website.
This includes software downloads, which are made available in
relation to purchased products. An assignment of solutions, some of
which are specially tailored to the customer, is only possible if the
user can be identified in this way.
Duration of retention
The data will be deleted as soon as it is no longer necessary to achieve the purpose for which it was collected.
This is the case for the data collected during the registration
process if the registration on our website is canceled or changed.
Right to objection and removal
As a user, you have the opportunity to cancel your registration at
any time. You can change the data stored about you at any time. To do
so, please contact our respective customer support.
CONTACT FORM AND E-MAIL CONTACTDescription and scope of data processing
A contact form, which can be used for electronic contact, is
available on our website. If a user uses this, the data entered in the
input mask will be transmitted to us and stored. This data includes:
(1) Title(2) Name(3) Company name(4) Position(5) Phone number(6) E-mail address(7) Message
At the time the message is sent, the following data is also stored:
(1) The IP address of the user(2) Date and time of registration
Your consent is obtained for the processing of the data during the sending process and reference is made to this Privacy Policy.
Alternatively, you can contact us via the e-mail address provided. In
that case, the user's personal data transmitted by e-mail will be
stored.
In this context, the data will not be passed on to third parties. The data is used exclusively for processing the conversation.
Legal basis for data processing
The legal basis for the processing of the data if the user has given their consent is Art. 6 (1) (a) GDPR.
The legal basis for the processing of data transmitted in the course
of sending an e-mail is Art. 6 (1) (f) GDPR. If the e-mail contact aims
to conclude a contract, then the additional legal basis for the
processing is Art. 6 (1) (b) GDPR.
Purpose of data processing
The processing of the personal data from the input mask only serves
the aim of processing the establishment of contact. In the event of
contact by e-mail, this also constitutes the necessary legitimate
interest in the processing of the data.
The other personal data processed during the sending process serves
to prevent misuse of the contact form and to ensure the security of our
information technology systems.
Duration of retention
The data will be deleted as soon as it is no longer necessary to
achieve the purpose for which it was collected. For the personal data
from the input mask of the contact form and that which was sent by
e-mail, this is the case when the respective conversation with the user
is finished. The conversation is terminated when it can be inferred from
the circumstances that the facts in question have been finally
clarified.
The additional personal data collected during the sending process will be deleted after a period of seven days at the latest.
Right to objection and removal
The user has the possibility to revoke his or her consent to the
processing of personal data at any time. If the user contacts us by
e-mail, he/she can object to the storage of his or her personal data at
any time. In such a case, the conversation cannot be continued.
To revoke your consent or to object to the storage of data, contact
us using the contact form or by mail or e-mail at the addresses
provided.
All personal data stored in the course of contacting us will be deleted in this case.
RIGHTS OF THE DATA SUBJECTWhere your personal data is processed, you are deemed to be a
data subject as defined in the GDPR and you have the following rights
vis-a-vis the controller:
Right to information
You can request confirmation from the controller regarding whether your personal data is being processed by us.
If such processing has taken place, you can request the following information from the controller:
(1) the purposes for which the personal data is being processed;(2) the categories of personal data being processed;(3) the recipients and/or categories of recipients to whom your personal data has been or will be disclosed;(4) the
planned storage period for your personal data or, if no concrete
information can be provided in this regard, criteria for determining the
storage period;(5) the
existence of the right to request from the controller rectification or
erasure of personal data, or restriction of processing of personal data
concerning the data subject, or to object to such processing; (6) the right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority;(7) any available information on the origin of the data if the personal data is not collected from the data subject;(8) the
existence of automated decision-making, including profiling, referred
to in Art. 22 (1) and (4) GDPR and, at least in those cases, meaningful
information about the logic involved, as well as the significance and
the envisaged consequences of such processing for the data subject.
You have the right to request information about whether your personal
data is transmitted to a non-EU country or an international
organization. In this context, you may request to be informed of the
appropriate guarantees pursuant to Art. 46 GDPR in connection with the
transmission.
Right to rectification
You have a right of rectification and/or completion vis-à-vis the
data controller if the personal data processed concerning you is
incorrect or incomplete. The controller shall make the correction
without undue delay.
Right to restriction of processing
Under the following conditions, you may request that the processing of your personal data be restricted:
(1) if you dispute the accuracy
of the personal data concerning you for a period of time that enables
the data controller to verify the accuracy of the personal data;(2) if
the processing is unlawful and you refuse to delete the personal data
and instead request that the use of the personal data be restricted;(3) if
the controller no longer needs the personal data for the purposes of
the processing, but you do need them to assert, exercise or defend legal
claims, or(4) if
you have objected to processing pursuant to Art. 21 (1) GDPR pending
the verification of whether the legitimate grounds of the controller
override those of the data subject.
If the processing of your personal data has been limited, this data –
aside from its storage – may only be processed with your consent or in
order to assert, exercise or defend legal claims or to protect the
rights of another natural or legal person, or for the sake of an
important public interest of the Union or a member state.
If the processing restriction has been imposed according to the
aforementioned conditions, you will be informed by the data controller
before the restriction is lifted.
Right to deletion
a) Obligation to delete data
You may request the data controller to delete the personal data
relating to you without delay and the controller is obligated to delete
this data without delay if one of the following reasons applies:
(1) The personal data concerning you is no longer necessary for the purposes for which it was collected or otherwise processed.(2) You
revoke your consent, on which the processing was based, pursuant to
Art. 6 (1) (a) or Art. 9 (2) (a) GDPR, and there is no other legal basis
for processing. (3) You
file an objection against the processing pursuant to Art. 21 (1) GDPR
and there are no overriding legitimate reasons for processing, or you
file an objection against the processing pursuant to Art. 21 (2) GDPR. (4) The personal data concerning you has been processed unlawfully. (5) Your
personal data must be erased for compliance with a legal obligation in
Union or Member State law to which the controller is subject. (6) Your
personal data has been collected in relation to the offer of
information society services referred to in Art. 8 (1) of the GDPR.
b) Information to third parties
If the data controller has made the personal data concerning you
public and is obliged to delete it pursuant to Art. 17 (1) GDPR, it
shall take appropriate measures, including technical measures, taking
into account the available technology and the implementation costs, to
inform data processors who process the personal data that you, as the
data subject, have requested the deletion of, all links to this personal
data, or of copies or replications of the personal data.
c) Exemptions
The right to deletion does not exist insofar as the processing is necessary
(1) for exercising freedom of expression and information;(2) for
compliance with a legal obligation which requires processing by Union
or Member State law to which the controller is subject or for the
performance of a task carried out in the public interest or in the
exercise of official authority vested in the controller;(3) for reasons of public interest in the field of public health pursuant to Art. 9 (2) (h) and (i) and Art. 9 (3) GDPR;(4) for
archiving purposes in the public interest, scientific or historical
research purposes or for statistical purposes pursuant to Art. 89 (1)
GDPR, insofar as the law referred to under a) is likely to render
impossible or seriously impair the attainment of the objectives of such
processing, or(5) to assert, exercise or defend legal claims.
Right to notification
If you have exercised your right to have the data controller
corrected, deleted or limit the processing, it is obliged to inform all
recipients to whom the personal data concerning you has been disclosed
of this correction or deletion of the data or restriction on processing,
unless this proves impossible or involves a disproportionate effort.
You have the right to be informed by the data controller of such recipients.
Right to data transferability
You have the right to receive your personal data that you have
provided to the controller in a structured, conventional, and
machine-readable format. In addition, you have the right to pass this
data on to another controller without hindrance by the controller to
whom the personal data was provided, as long as
(1) the processing is based on a
declaration of consent pursuant to Art. 6 (1) (a) GDPR or Art. 9 (2)
(a) GDPR or on a contract pursuant to Art. 6 (1) (b) GDPR and(2) processing is carried out using automated methods.
In exercising this right, you also have the right to request that
your personal data be transferred directly from one data controller to
another, insofar as this is technically feasible. This should not impair
other people's freedoms or rights.
The right to transferability shall not apply to the processing of
personal data necessary for the performance of a task in the public
interest or in the exercise of official authority vested in the
controller.
Right to object
On grounds relating to your particular situation, You have the right
to object, at any time, to the processing of your personal data based on
Art. 6 (1) (e) or (f) GDPR, including profiling based on those
provisions.
The data controller no longer processes the personal data concerning
you unless it can prove compelling, legitimate reasons for the
processing, which override your interests, rights and freedoms, or the
processing serves to assert, exercise or defend legal claims.
If your personal data is being processed for the purpose of direct
marketing, you have the right to object at any time to the processing of
your personal data for the purpose of such advertising; this also
applies to profiling where this is connected to such direct marketing.
If you object to the processing for direct marketing purposes, your
personal data will no longer be processed for these purposes.
You have the opportunity to exercise your right of objection in
connection with the use of Information Society services by means of
automated procedures using technical specifications, notwithstanding
Directive 2002/58/EC.
Right to revoke the declaration of consent on data protection
You have the right to revoke your data protection declaration of
consent at any time. Revoking your consent will not affect the legality
of any processing that took place before the revocation.
Automated decision in individual cases including profiling
You have the right not to be subject to a decision based exclusively
on automated processing – including profiling – that has legal effect
against you or significantly impairs you in a similar manner. This does
not apply if the decision
(1) is necessary for the conclusion or performance of a contract between you and the controller,(2) is
admissible by law of the Union or of the Member States to which the
controller is subject and that law contains appropriate measures to
safeguard your rights, freedoms and legitimate interests, or(3) with your express consent.
However, these decisions may not be based on special categories of
personal data pursuant to Art. 9 (1) GDPR, unless Art. 9 (2) (a) or (g)
applies and appropriate measures have been taken to protect your rights
and freedoms and your legitimate interests.
In the cases referred to in (1) and (3), the controller shall take
reasonable measures to safeguard your rights, freedoms and legitimate
interests, including, at minimum, the right to obtain the intervention
of a person by the controller, to state his or her point of view and to
challenge the decision.
Right to lodge a complaint with a supervisory authority
Without prejudice to any other administrative or judicial remedy, you
have the right of appeal to a supervisory authority, in particular in
the Member State where you reside, work, or where the suspected
infringement took place, if you believe that the processing of your
personal data is contrary to the GDPR.
The supervisory authority to which the complaint has been lodged
shall inform the complainant of the status and results of the complaint,
including the possibility of a judicial remedy under Article 78 GDPR.
Concept, Design, Programming:graphodata AG – TYPO3, Magento, Shopware, Fullservice Internet Agency
Technical questions concerning this site should be directed to:info@graphodata.de
print page
Facts> 40Subsidiaries on five continents> 290engine | powertrain test cells> 6700employees worldwideGroupFEV Consulting
FEV DLP
etamax
Share 2 Drive
EVA
B&W
S&B
CreltecSolutionsEngineering ServicesSoftware and Testing SolutionsContactFEV Group GmbH Neuenhofstraße 181 52078 Aachen, GermanyPhone +49 241 5689 0Contact us
FEV North America Inc.4554 Glenmeade LaneAuburn Hills, MI 48326-1766Phone +1 248 373-6000marketing_fev@fev.com
Further locations Legal Notice & Data Protection | Copyright & Trademark | Conditions of Purchase
Who we are | What we do | Press | Careers | Contact | Home+ Show SitemapWhat we doVehicle DevelopmentPowertrain Development & ElectrificationIntelligent Mobility & SoftwareSoftware and Testing SolutionsConsultingWho we areManagementLocationsValuesCompany HistoryQuality, Project Management, Occupational & Environmental SafetyCareersCurrent OpeningsUnsolicited ApplicationIntroducing FEVRecruitment EventsContactComing upFEV ConferencesExhibitionsOnline SeminarsWhitepapersCustomer NewslettersPressCorona Information
What we doVehicle DevelopmentVehicle ArchitectureChassis and Electric & ElectronicsBody in WhiteExterior and InteriorLightingVehicle PerformanceProductionPowertrain Development & ElectrificationAerodynamics & Flow AnalysesAdvanced ApplicationsBenchmarkingCommercial and Industrial PowertrainsE-MobilityFuel CellE-DriveBattery DevelopmentFuelsLarge Bore EnginesNVH – Noise Vibration HarshnessOff-HighwayLegislation, Acceptance, Market DemandsEffiency & CostsUse of New TechnologiesIndustry 4.0 / 5Passenger Car & Light Commercial Diesel PowertrainsPassenger Car Gasoline PowertrainsProduction & Value EngineeringTransmission SystemsTurbochargingIntelligent Mobility & SoftwareAssisted & Automated DrivingConnected MobilitySystems EngineeringFunctional SafetyCybersecurityVehicles ElectronicsSoftwareData ScienceSoftware and Testing SolutionsTest CenterTest BenchesProductsSimulationTestingAutomated Test SystemsService and MaintenanceDownload CenterEmbedded Systems DevelopmentContactConsultingWho we areManagementLocationsGermanyAachenAlsdorfBrunswickDarmstadtGerlingenHeilbronnIngolstadtLandsbergMunichRüsselsheimSandersdorf-BrehnaSiersdorf-AldenhovenStuttgartWolfsburgUSAAuburn Hills - Vehicle Development CenterRochester HillsChinaBeijingDalianGuangzhouShanghaiWuhanChongqingFranceSaint-Quentin-en-YvelinesRouenToulouseIndiaPuneChennaiNoidaAustriaSteyrBrazilValinhosS. J. dos CamposCuritibaItalyTurinJapanTokyoMexicoPueblaNetherlandsHelmondPolandKrakowRomaniaBucharestTimisoaraRussiaMoscowSouth KoreaBundangSpainBarcelonaSwedenGothenburgTrollhättanTaiwanTaoyuanThailandSrirachaTurkeyIstanbulUnited KingdomCoventryVietnamHanoiValuesCompany HistoryQuality, Project Management, Occupational & Environmental SafetyCareersCurrent OpeningsJobs in EuropeJobs in AsiaJobs in AmericaUnsolicited ApplicationIntroducing FEVRecruitment EventsContactComing upFEV ConferencesFEV Conference - Zero CO2 MobilityIntroductionConference ProgramRegistrationScientific CommitteeSponsoring OpportunitiesPress & MediaImpressions 2019FEV Conference - Diesel Powertrains 3.0IntroductionConference ProgramRegistrationScientific CommiteeImpressions 2019Aachen Acoustics ColloquiumFEV Tech DaysEuropeAsiaExhibitionsOnline SeminarsWhitepapersShared MobilityEnergy StorageHigh Tech or Low CostCustomer NewslettersFEV SpectrumFEV Spectrum ArchivesFEV China NewsletterEngineering NewsletterPressPress ReleasesPress mailing listYour ContactCorona Information Languages & Countries
EnglishGermanChineseJapaneseLocationsGermanyUSABrazilUnited KingdomSwedenFranceItalySpainPolandRomaniaChinaIndiaJapanTurkeyTaiwan
